//question
const assamhistory=[
    {"question":"When did Muhammad-bin-Bkhtiyar Khalji Proceeded Eastward into Assam?",
       "options":["1204","1205","1206","1207"],
       "answer":"1206",
       "number":"one"
    },
    {"question":"Who was the king of Kamrupa during Bakhtiyar Khalji's invasion in Assam?",
    "options":["Prithu","Sandhya","Durlabh Narayan","Rup Naryan"],
    "answer":"Prithu",
    "number":"two"
 },
 {
   "question":"Which of the following ruler was popularly known as 'Lord of Gaur'? ",
   "options":["Durlabh Narayan","Dharma Narayan","Chandibar","Chilarai"],
   "answer":"Dharma Narayan",
   "number":"three"
 },
 {
   "question":"Ram Saraswati,Harihar Vipra and Hem Saraswati were the court poets of which Kamata ruler?",
   "options":["Indra Narayan","Dharma Narayan","Durlabh Narayan"],
   "answer":"Durlabh Narayan",
   "number":"four"
 },
 {
   "question":"Who has established Cuttiya kingdom?",
   "options":["Nitya Pal","Birpal","Nyayapal"],
   "answer":"Birpal",
   "number":"five"
 },
 {
   "question":"In which day Sati Sadhni Divas celebrate?",
   "options":["24 April","21 April","24 May"],
   "answer":"21 April",
   "number":"six"
 },
 {
   "question":"What was the real name of King Nara Narayan?",
   "options":["Narasingh","Sukhladhwaja","Malladeva"],
   "answer":"Malladeva",
   "number":"seven"
 },
 {
   "question":"Gohain Kamal Ali from Koch-Behar to Narayanpur was constructed during the reign of",
   "options":["Nara Narayana","Dharma Narayan","Durlabh Narayan"],
   "answer":"Nara Narayana",
   "number":"eight"
 },
 {
   "question":"What was the real name of Chilarai?",
   "options":["Sukhladhwaja","Biswa Singha","Malladeva"],
   "answer":"Sukhladhwaja",
   "number":"nine"
 },
 {
   "question":"Chao Suhungmung was the first Ahom King to adopt a Hindu title,indicating a move towards an inclusive polity.Which Hindu name did he take?",
   "options":["Swarga Narayan","Udayaditya Singha","Dhurlabh Narayana"],
   "answer":"Swarga Narayan",
   "number":"ten"
 },
 {
   "question":"Which of the folllowing Ahom ruler was known as 'Lora Raja'(Boy King)?",
   "options":["Sulikpha","Sujinpha","Suklampha"],
   "answer":"Sulikpha",
   "number":"eleven"
 },
 {
   "question":"Who was sent with force to help the Manipuri King during the reign of Rajeswar Singha?",
   "options":["Kirti Chamdra","Rudra Singha","Haranath Senapati"],
   "answer":"Haranath Senapati",
   "number":"twelve"
 },
 {
   "question":"How many days did Captain Thomas Welsh styed in Assam during the reign of Gaurinath Singha?",
   "options":["12Month","20Month","17Month"],
   "answer":"17Month",
   "number":"thirteen"
 },
 {
   "question":"Who was the first Ahom ruler who stikes coins?",
   "options":["Sulikpha","Sudangpha","Garhgayan Raja"],
   "answer":"Garhgayan Raja",
   "number":"fourteen"
 },
 {
   "question":"Ghilajharighat Treaty was signed in",
   "options":["23January 1663","23August 1257","21January 1662"],
   "answer":"23January 1663",
   "number":"fifteen"
 },
  {
   "question":"Who was the first Bar Raja",
   "options":["Sarbeswari","Deopadi","Phuleswari Devi"],
   "answer":"Phuleswari Devi",
   "number":"sixteen"
 },
  {
   "question":"Who was known as Bamuni Konwar?",
   "options":["Sudangpha","Dhingia Raja","Sulikpha"],
   "answer":"Sudangpha",
   "number":"seventeen"
 },
  {
   "question":"The Battle of Saraighat between Ahoms and Mughals was fought in the year",
   "options":["1670","1671","1663"],
   "answer":"1671",
   "number":"eightteen"
 },
 {
   "question":"Which of the following Chief Queen of Ahom was constructed 'Shiva Doul' at Sivasagar?",
   "options":["Deopadi","Phuleswari Devi","Sarbeswari"],
   "answer":"Deopadi",
   "number":"nineteen"
 },
  {
   "question":"Kabiraj Chakravorty was patron by",
   "options":["Rudra Singha","Rajeswar Singha","Pramatta Singha"],
   "answer":"Rudra Singha",
   "number":"twenty"
 },
 


 ]
 
 const quant=[
    {"question":"Shivam's expense is 25% more than Ramesh's expenses and Ramesh's expense is 15% less than Rupam's expenses.If the sum of their expense is Rs4660,then what would be the shivam's expenses?",
       "options":["Rs1360","Rs1700","Rs1600","Rs1156"],
       "answer":"Rs1700",
       "number":"one"
    },
    {
       "question":"Population of a city increses 20% every year,find the population of city after 2years if present population of a city is 15000?",
       "options":["20600","21600","22600","19600"],
       "answer":'21600',
       "number":"two"
    },
    {
      "question":"A and B both spend 30% of their income together which is equal to Rs 26400.If income of A is 20% more than that of B then find the income of B?",
      "options":["52000","48000","40000"],
      "answer":"40000",
      "number":"three"
    },
    {
      "question":"Cost price of 2 bags is in ratio 4:5 and these bags are sold at 10% profit & 20% profit respectively.Find overall profit percentage in entire transaction.",
      "options":["15 5/9%","12 5/9%","14 5/9%"],
      "answer":"15 5/9%",
      "number":"four"
    },
    {
      "question":"Ram sold one article at 33 1/3% profit and another at 100% profit.Find his overall profit percentage if the selling price of both the article is same?",
      "options":["56%","60%","40%"],
      "answer":"60%",
      "number":"five"
    },
    {
      "question":"Marked price of an article is Rs 250 more than cost price of that article and it is sold at a discount of 15% on marked price.Find the cost price of the article if profit percentage earned is 27.5%?",
      "options":["500","600","400"],
      "answer":"500",
      "number":"six"
    },
    {
      "question":"Rohit received Rs3456 when he invested Rs P at 12% p.a at SI for 3 years.If he invested Rs(P+4400) at 15% p.a at CI compounding annually for 2 years,then find the interest received by him?",
      "options":["4960","4515","None"],
      "answer":"4515",
      "number":"seven"
    },
    {
      "question":"Difference of CI received in first year and second year at 20% per annum at CI is Rs 1200 then find the sum?",
      "options":["30000","60000","40000"],
      "answer":"30000",
      "number":"eight"
    },
    {
      "question":"An amount of Rs 4000 is invested at 20% per annum for 2 years at CI half-yearly,then find the total interest amount received after 2 years?",
      "options":["18550","18125","18564"],
      "answer":"18564",
      "number":"nine"
    },
    {
      "question":"What is the interest earned by Rupam on 10000 Rupees for the period of 2 years at the rate of 12.5% SI?",
      "options":["2000","3000","2500"],
      "answer":"2500",
      "number":"ten"
    },
 ]

 export {assamhistory,quant}